Jordan Stewart design • ux • illustration

About Me _____

Hello! I am Jordan Stewart and I attend Kent State University in Kent, Ohio where I major in Visual Communication Design and minor in User Experience Design. Art, design and coffee are the things that make me get out of bed in the morning. I absolutely love what I do and hope to help as many people as I possibly can through design.

Contact



Email:

jstewa61@kent.edu

Phone:

(440)-610-7789

Website:

jordanstewartdesign.com

Work Experience ___

Graphic Designer, Kent State Athletics Marketing – 2017–Present design promotional marketing materials for Kent State Athletics

Supervisor, Common Ground Canopy Tours - 2016-Present

oversee canopy tour operations, give tours, answer phones, course maintenance

Education

Kent State University – 2015-Present

Bachelor of Fine Arts in Visual Communication Design with a minor in User Experience Design

Skills

Graphic Design, Illustration, User Experience Design

have completed coursework in typography, graphic design, responsive web design and illustration, and know HTML and CSS

Software

Adobe Creative Suite (InDesign, Illustrator, Photoshop, Lightroom, After Effects, Xd), Atom

Awards + Achievements

- Featured in the Fall 2017 Kent State VCD Juried Show
- Lorain Arts Council Graphic Design Scholarship
- Kent State Deans List Fall 2015 to Spring 2017
- Eagle Scout